A Register of the Claude Paillat Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Research materials, 1863-1999 (Folder 1-414)
  - Énergie, 1970-1982 (Folder 49-50)
    - Recherche et production, 1970-1974 (Folder 50: 1)
    - Compagnies petrolières, 1973-1982 (Folder 50: 2)
    - Rapport Schwartz, 1974 (Folder 50: 3)
    - Nucléaire, 1973-1980 (Folder 50: 4)
    - Actions antinucléaires, 1977-1980 (Folder 50: 5)
    - Socialistes, 1981-1982 (Folder 50: 6)
    - Organisation des Pays Exportateurs du Pétrole (O.P.E.P.), 1981 (Folder 50: 7)
  - Enregistrements (audiocassettes, 1967-1980 (Folder 134-146)
    - Entretiens, 1937-1980 (Folder 134-145)
      - Albisetti, [?], 1976 (Folder 134: 7-8)
      - Allain des Beauvais, [?], 1977 (Folder 134: 9)
      - Amieux, Jean-Maurice, 1979 (Folder 134: 10)
      - Artur, Pierre, 1980 (Folder 134: 11)
      - Aujol, Jean-Louis, Mme., 1980 (Folder 134: 12)
      - Babin-Chevaye, [?], 1977 (Folder 134: 13-14)
      - Bariéty, [?], 1976 (Folder 134: 15-16)
      - Barrelet-Clémentel, [?], 1979 (Folder 135: 1)
      - Bayart, Philippe, 1977 (Folder 135: 2-6)
      - Beaufort-Lienart, Claude, 1979 (Folder 135: 7)
      - Bernardet, Jean, 1979 (Folder 135: 8)
      - Besineau, Michel, 1976 (Folder 135: 9-12)
      - Bonvoisin, [?], 1977 (Folder 135: 13-14)
      - Bonnefon-Crappone, Jean, 1976 (Folder 135: 15-16)
      - Boumier, [?], 1977 (Folder 135: 17-18.)
      - Boussac, Jean-Claude, 1979 (Folder 135: 19-20)
      - Boussac, Jean-Claude, 1979 (Folder 136: 1-8)
      - Branca, Guy, 1994 (Folder 136: 9-12)
      - Briton [?], [?] Beaupère, et [?] Horeau, 1976 (Folder 136: 13)
      - Bruneau, J., 1977 (Folder 136: 14-15)
      - Brunner, Gabriel, 1977 (Folder 136: 16)
      - Brusaut, Pierre, 1978 (Folder 136: 17-18)
      - Cado, [?], 1978 (Folder 136: 19)
      - Caquot, A., 1976 (Folder 136: 20-21)
      - Catta, [?], 1978 (Folder 136: 22)
      - Chapelle, de la, 1977 (Folder 137: 1-2)
      - Chapon, Richard, 1978 (Folder 137: 3-6)
      - Chautemps, Jean, 1977 (Folder 137: 7-8)
      - Chesné, André, 1979 (Folder 137: 9-10)
      - Chrétien, J., 1978 (Folder 137: 11-12)
      - Clementin, [?], 1978 (Folder 137: 13)
      - Cossé, Georges, 1977 (Folder 137: 14)
      - Cottin, Philippe, 1979 (Folder 137: 15)
      - Courrech, Robert, 1978 (Folder 137: 16-17)
      - Courville, Luce, 1976 (Folder 137: 18)
      - Croisier, [?], 1976 (Folder 137: 19)
      - Decré, Emile, 1976 (Folder 137: 20-21)
      - Decré, Emile, Mme., 1977 (Folder 137: 22-23)
      - Delafoy, [?], 1976 (Folder 138: 1-2)
      - Delmasure, Adolphe, 1977 (Folder 138: 3-4)
      - Delmasure, Adophe et Debusche, 1967 (Folder 138: 5)
      - Duclos-Prax, Mme., 1976 (Folder 138: 6)
      - Dufourg, [?], 1978 (Folder 138: 7-8)
      - Dumortier, Jacques, 1976 (Folder 138: 9)
      - Duprez, [?], 1976 (Folder 138: 10)
      - Durand-Perdriel, René, 1976 (Folder 138: 11-12)
      - Favreau, Bertrand, 1978 (Folder 138: 13-14)
      - Feraud-Prax, [?], 1978 (Folder 138: 15)
      - Georges, France, 1977-1978 (Folder 138: 16-19)
      - Géraud, André, 1977 (Folder 138: 20-22)
      - Glorieux, [?], 1976 (Folder 139: 1-2)
      - Grandjouan, Paul, 1977 (Folder 139: 3-4)
      - Greffeuille, Marcel, 1978 (Folder 139: 5-6)
      - Guibal, [?], 1977 (Folder 139: 7-8)
      - Guiral, Pierre, 1979 (Folder 139: 9-10)
      - Hederer, Fernand, 1978 (Folder 139: 11-18)
      - Hersant, Robert, 1978 (Folder 139: 19)
      - Huguier, [?], 1978 (Folder 139: 20-21)
      - Lawton, Mme., 1978 (Folder 139: 22)
      - Lawton, Hugues, 1978 (Folder 140: 1-7)
      - Lecomte, Jean, 1979 (Folder 140: 8-10)
      - Lefévre-Utile, Michel, 1977 (Folder 140: 11-16)
      - Lehideux, François, 1977 (Folder 140: 17)
      - Lenard, André, 1979 (Folder 140: 18)
      - Lenoir, Mme., 1979 (Folder 140: 19)
      - Lepeltier, [?], 1977 (Folder 140: 20-21)
      - Lerat, Bernard, 1977-1978 (Folder 141: 1-5)
      - Lestienne, [?], 1977 (Folder 141: 6-7)
      - Loew, Jacques, 1980 (Folder 141: 8-9)
      - Loizillon, André, 1981 (Folder 141: 10)
      - Mallet, Xavier, 1978 (Folder 141: 11-18)
      - Maréchal, [?], 1976 (Folder 141: 19)
      - Martin, [?], 1977 (Folder 141: 20-21)
      - Mayrisch, Arbed, 1978 (Folder 141: 22)
      - Mérieux, Charles, 1979 (Folder 142: 1)
      - Meyer, Jacques, 1978 (Folder 142: 2-5)
      - Milani, Pierre, 1978 (Folder 142: 6-9)
      - Morault, [?], 1977 (Folder 142: 10)
      - Motte, B., 1977 (Folder 142: 11-12)
      - Neumann, T., 1978 (Folder 142: 13-14)
      - Nondin-Pierre, Jean, 1978 (Folder 142: 15-16)
      - Paget, [?], 1978 (Folder 142: 17-19)
      - Parseval, R. P. de, 1978 (Folder 142: 20-21)
      - Pellegrini, [?], 1977 (Folder 142: 22)
      - Pennel, [?], 1976 (Folder 143: 1-2)
      - Petitjean, [?], 1977 (Folder 143: 3-4)
      - Polo, Marc, 1977-1978 (Folder 143: 5-8)
      - Polo, Philippe, 1978 (Folder 143: 9-10)
      - Potez, Henri, 1978 (Folder 143: 11-12)
      - Puiseux, Robert, 1977 (Folder 143: 13-14)
        Use copy reference number: 2008c38_a_0007828
        Includes sound recording of interview of Puiseux by Paillat, 17 June 1977. In French. 2 compact sound cassettes.
      - Raingeard, Michel, 1977-1978 (Folder 143: 15-16)
      - Ramarony, Jules, Mme., 1978 (Folder 143: 17)
      - Reinard, [?], 1978 (Folder 143: 18)
      - Remusat, Mme., 1979 (Folder 143: 19)
      - Reul, Albert, 1979 (Folder 143: 20-22)
      - Reul, Albert, 1979 (Folder 144: 1-4)
      - Riou, [?], 1976 (Folder 144: 5-6)
      - Rivet-Houtin, [?], 1979 (Folder 144: 7)
      - Rochut, [?], 1977 (Folder 144: 8)
      - Rothschild, Philippe de, 1979 (Folder 144: 9-10)
      - Rouchet, [?], 1977 (Folder 144: 11)
      - Roux, Edmond, 1978 (Folder 144: 12)
      - Sabiani, Mlle., 1979 (Folder 144: 13)
      - Screpel, [?], 1977 (Folder 144: 14-15)
      - Segogne, [?], 1977 (Folder 144: 16-17)
      - Setout, Léon, 1978 (Folder 144: 18)
      - Sire, Pierre, 1978 (Folder 144: 19-20)
      - Sire, Pierre et Hugues Lawton, 1979 (Folder 144: 21-22)
      - Taittinger, Jean, 1978 (Folder 145: 1-2)
      - Taittinger, Jean et Mlle. Ponthieu, 1978 (Folder 145: 3)
      - Taittinger, Pierre, Mme., 1978 (Folder 145: 4)
      - Trarieux-Lumière, Maurice, 1979 (Folder 145: 5-6)
      - [?] et François Lehideux, 1977 (Folder 145: 7-9)
      - Vidal, [?] et François Lehideux, 1978 (Folder 145: 10-11)
      - Zalkind, [?] et [?] Riou, 1976 (Folder 145: 12-14)
      - Zarifi, Georges-Michel, 1978 (Folder 145: 15)
    - Divers, 1970-1980 (Folder 145-146)
      - Bordeaux, 1980 (Folder 145: 16-17)
      - Calais, 1976 (Folder 145: 18)
      - Carpentier, Marcel-Maurice, 1979 (Folder 145: 19)
      - Carré, Mathilde et Pierre de Crevoisier de Vomécourt, 1979 (Folder 145: 20-22)
      - "Comprendre Aujourd'hui,", 1980 (Folder 146: 1-4)
      - L'Écho du nord, 1979 (Folder 146: 5)
      - Garrigues, 1978 (Folder 146: 6)
      - "Les Matinées de France Culture,", 1981 (Folder 146: 7-8)
      - Paillat, Claude, 1970 (Folder 146: 9-13)
      - "Le Phare de la Loire,", 1978 (Folder 146: 14)
      - Soirée, 1978 (Folder 146: 15)
  - Enregistrements (audiocassettes), 1975-1994 (Folder 401-403)
    - Entretiens, 1975-1994 (Folder 401-403)
      - Albisetti, [?], 1976 (Folder 401: 1)
      - Aujol, Jean-Louis, Mme., 1979-1980 (Folder 401: 2-4)
      - Auphan, Georgi, 1986 (Folder 401: 5-6)
      - Boulnois, Francis, 1988 (Folder 401: 7-8)
      - Branca, Guy, 1994 (Folder 401: 9)
      - Brohon, Raymond, 1982 (Folder 401: 10-13)
      - Carré, Paul, 1979 (Folder 401: 14-16)
      - Chamant, [?], 1978 (Folder 401: 17)
      - Chevalier, Alain, 1980 (Folder 401: 18-21)
      - Desgrées du Lou, François, 1980 (Folder 401: 22)
      - Fournier, Lucien, 1986 (Folder 402: 1)
      - Fréville, Henri, 1980 (Folder 402: 2)
      - Ginestet, Bernard, 1979 (Folder 402: 3)
      - Ginestet, Pierre, 1979 (Folder 402: 4-5)
      - Graux, Pierre, 1979 (Folder 402: 6)
      - Halley, [?], 1990 (Folder 402: 7)
      - Humbert, Jean, 1984 (Folder 402: 8)
      - Huntziger, Jacques, 1983 (Folder 402: 9-10)
      - Huron, Louis, 1992 (Folder 402: 11)
      - La Grange, Amaury de, 1982 (Folder 402: 12)
      - Le Nan, [?], 1984 (Folder 402: 13-14)
      - Leroy Ladurie, Jacques, 1982 (Folder 402: 15-16)
      - Letourneau, Jean, 1988 (Folder 402: 17)
      - Leygues, Jacques Raphaël, 1986 (Folder 402: 18)
      - Lombares, Michel de, 1982 (Folder 402: 19-20)
      - Maud-huy, Bertrand de, 1981 (Folder 402: 21)
      - Mollans, Henri de, 1984 (Folder 402: 22)
      - Nguyen-Dê, [?], 1980 (Folder 403: 1-2)
      - Paillat, Claude, 1986 (Folder 403: 3)
      - Prouvost, Albert, 1982 (Folder 403: 4)
      - Renauld, Pierre, 1983 (Folder 403: 5-6)
      - Rivière, P., 1991 (Folder 403: 7-8)
      - Robichon, [?], 1979 (Folder 403: 9-10)
      - Roos, Joseph, 1982 (Folder 403: 11)
      - Serrou, Robert, 1982 (Folder 403: 12-14)
      - Sesmaisons, Yves de, 1986 (Folder 403: 15)
      - Stenger, Abbé, 1980 (Folder 403: 16)
      - Tilroy, Jean, 1982 (Folder 403: 17)
      - Ullmo, Jean, 1975 (Folder 403: 18-19)
      - Van Anthyme, [?], 1981 (Folder 403: 20)
      - Yrissou, [?], 1986 (Folder 403: 21)
    - Divers, 1976 (Folder 403)
      - Marseilles, 1976 (Folder 22-23: 16-17)
  - Enseignement, 1969-1982 (Folder 41-42)
    - Générale, 1969-1981 (Folder 41: 1)
    - Enseignants, 1969-1980 (Folder 41: 2)
    - Grèves, 1978-1979 (Folder 41: 3)
    - École et la presse, 1978-1979 (Folder 41: 4)
    - École et monde du travail, 1977-1979 (Folder 41: 5)
    - Faits divers, 1969-1979 (Folder 41: 6)
    - Lois et réformes, 1969-1972 (Folder 41: 7)
    - Enseignement libre et enseignement privé, 1970-1979 (Folder 41: 8)
    - Éducation nationale, 1970-1979 (Folder 41: 9)
    - Réforme Haby, 1974-1975 (Folder 41: 10)
    - Agitation dans les lycées, 1969-1974 (Folder 41)
      - 1969-1970 (Folder 41: 11)
      - 1971 (Folder 41: 12-13)
      - 1972-1974 (Folder 41: 14)
    - Université de Vincennes, 1970-1980 (Folder 42: 1)
    - Université de Nanterre, 1970-1971 (Folder 42: 2-4)
    - Polytechnique, 1970-1977 (Folder 42: 5)
    - Étudiants et l'emploi, 1970-1972 (Folder 42: 6)
    - Manifestations contre la loi Debré, 1973 (Folder 42: 7)
    - Réformes universitaires, 1970-1971 (Folder 42: 8)
    - Sexologie, 1973-1975 (Folder 42: 9)
    - Agitation dans les universités, 1970-1973 (Folder 42: 10)
    - Agitation dans les universités de province, 1969-1972 (Folder 42: 11)
    - Agitation dans le Quartier Latin, 1970-1971 (Folder 42: 12)
    - Élections universitaires, 1970-1971 (Folder 42: 13)
    - Faculté des Sciences de Paris, 1969-1972 (Folder 42: 14)
    - Université d'Assas, 1970 (Folder 42: 15)
    - Université de Censier, 1969-1972 (Folder 42: 16)
    - Université Paris-Dauphine, 1969-1971 (Folder 42: 17)
    - École Normale Supérieure, 1970-1971 (Folder 42: 18)
    - École des Mines, 1974-1982 (Folder 42: 19)
    - Syndicats étudiants, 1969-1971 (Folder 42: 20)
    - Petites et grandes écoles, 1981 (Folder 42: 21)
  - États-Unis, 1903-1975 (Folder 303, 335-337, 406)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1974 (Folder 303: 1)
    - Rapports américains, 1930-1939 (Folder 303)
      - Maroc, 1936-1938 (Folder 303: 2)
      - Syrie-Liban, 1930-1939 (Folder 303)
        - 1930 (Folder 303: 3)
        - 1931 (Folder 303: 4)
        - 1932 (Folder 303: 5)
        - 1933 (Folder 303: 6)
        - 1934 (Folder 303: 7)
        - 1935 (Folder 303: 8)
        - 1936 (Folder 303: 9)
        - 1937 (Folder 303: 10)
        - 1938 (Folder 303: 11)
        - 1939 (Folder 303: 12)
    - Notes, 1975 (Folder 335: 15)
    - Traité de Versailles, 1922-1923 (Folder 335: 16)
    - Jusserand, Jean Adrien Antoine Jules, 1903-1926 (Folder 335)
      - 1903-1924 (Folder 335: 17)
      - 1918 (Folder 335: 18)
      - 1919-1926 (Folder 335: 19)
    - Correspondance et rapports, 1942-1951 (Folder 336)
      - Générale, 1942-1951 (Folder 336)
        - 1942-1945 (Folder 336: 1)
        - 1944 (Folder 336: 2)
        - 1945 (Folder 336: 3-4)
        - 1946 (Folder 336: 5)
        - 1947 (Folder 336: 6)
        - 1948 (Folder 336: 7-8)
        - 1949-1951 (Folder 336: 9)
      - Indochine, 1945 (Folder 337: 1)
      - Vietnam, 1948-1949 (Folder 337: 2)
      - Bangkok, 1948 (Folder 337: 3)
      - New Delhi, 1945 (Folder 337: 4)
      - Chunking, 1945 (Folder 337: 5)
      - Nanking, 1947 (Folder 337: 6)
      - Washington, 1945-1949 (Folder 337: 7)
      - Tunis, 1945-1949 (Folder 337: 8)
      - Alger, 1945-1949 (Folder 337: 9)
    - Traité de Versailles, 1919-1920 (Folder 406: 8)
    - Bullit, William C., 1919 (Folder 406: 9)
    - Wilson, Woodrow, 1919-1920 (Folder 406: 10)
  - Évènements de 1940, 1940-1990 (Folder 363-364)
    - L'Hostis, Jean, 1990 (Folder 363: 4)
    - d'Ornano, [?], 1956 (Folder 363: 5)
    - Haubourdin, 1940-1983 (Folder 363: 6)
    - Goubard, 1990 (Folder 364: 1)
    - Leclerc de Hauteclocque, Philippe, 1940-1990 (Folder 364: 2)
    - Vouziers, 1990 (Folder 364: 3)
    - Metz, 1990 (Folder 364: 4)
    - Roucaud, Jean, 1990 (Folder 364: 5)
    - Moutis, J. des, 1990 (Folder 364: 6)
    - Martel, Thierry de, 1990 (Folder 364: 7)
    - Devos, Christian, 1990 (Folder 364: 8)
  - Faulques, Roger, 1964 (Folder 108: 6-8)
  - Finances, 1929-1981 (Folder 61-62)
    - Monnaie, 1970-1979 (Folder 61: 1)
    - Budgets de l'état, 1974-1980 (Folder 61: 2)
    - Or, 1975-1980 (Folder 61: 3)
    - Crédit, 1969-1978 (Folder 61: 4)
    - Cour des comptes, 1973 (Folder 61: 5)
    - Épargne, 1974-1978 (Folder 61: 6)
    - Scandales, 1969-1976 (Folder 61: 7)
    - Taxation, 1969-1975 (Folder 61: 8)
    - Avoir fiscal, 1972-1977 (Folder 61: 9)
    - Fiscalité, 1970-1979 (Folder 61: 10)
    - Fraude fiscale, 1970-1979 (Folder 61: 11)
    - Banques et banquiers, 1970-1980 (Folder 61: 12)
    - Banque de France, 1929-1933 (Folder 61: 13)
    - Caisse d'Épargne, 1930 (Folder 61: 14)
    - Échanges internationaux, 1932 (Folder 62: 1)
    - Banque Worms, 1978 (Folder 62: 2)
    - Paribas, 1981 (Folder 62: 3)
  - France II, rapports américains, 1929-1941 (Folder 95-96)
    - l'Armée française, 1929 (Folder 95: 15-16)
    - Politique militaire, 1930-1941 (Folder 96)
      - 1930 (Folder 96: 1)
      - 1931 (Folder 96: 2)
      - 1933-1935 (Folder 96: 3)
      - 1936-1939 (Folder 96: 4)
      - 1940-1941 (Folder 96: 5)
  - France-Documents américains, 1945-1949 (Folder 414: 4-6)
  - France Libre, 1940-1942 (Folder 34)
    - Générale, 1940-1942 (Folder 34: 6)
    - Levant, 1941 (Folder 34: 7)
    - Londres, 1940 (Folder 34: 8)
    - Archives Forces Françaises Libres, 1940-1943 (Folder 34: 9)
  - France-Rapports américains sur l'armée française, 1940-1942 (Folder 406-407)
    - 1919 (Folder 406: 11)
    - 1920 (Folder 406: 12)
    - 1921 (Folder 406: 13)
    - 1922 (Folder 406: 14)
    - 1923 (Folder 407: 1)
    - 1924 (Folder 407: 2)
    - 1925 (Folder 407: 3)
    - 1926 (Folder 407: 4)
    - 1927 (Folder 407: 5)
    - 1928 (Folder 407: 6)
  - Gaulle, Charles de, 1968-1980 (Folder 147, 33)
    - Mai 68, 1968 (Folder 147: 5)
    - Rapports du Sénat, 1968 (Folder 147: 6)
    - Pompidou, Georges, 1969 (Folder 147: 7)
    - Fabre-Luce, Alfred, 1969 (Folder 147: 8)
    - Économie, 1968-1969 (Folder 147: 9)
    - Campagne électorale, 1969 (Folder 147: 10)
    - Information, 1969 (Folder 147: 11)
    - Politique intérieure, 1969 (Folder 147: 12)
    - Générale, 1970-1979 (Folder 33: 6)
    - Attentats contre de Gaulle, 1970-1971 (Folder 33: 7)
    - Colonies, 1969-1972 (Folder 33: 8)
    - Pompidou, Georges, 1980 (Folder 33: 9)
    - Reynaud, Paul, 1980 (Folder 33: 10)
    - Sondages, 1969-1972 (Folder 33: 11)
    - Départ, 1969 (Folder 33: 12)
    - Disparition politique, 1970 (Folder 33: 13)
    - La mort, 1970 (Folder 33: 14)
  - Gaullisme, 1969-1980 (Folder 31-32)
    - Union pour la Défense de la République, 1969-1976 (Folder 31)
      - 1969-1972 (Folder 31: 7)
      - 1973-1976 (Folder 31: 8)
    - Rassemblement pour la République, 1976-1980 (Folder 31)
      - 1976-1979 (Folder 31: 9)
      - 1980 (Folder 31: 10)
    - Debré, Michel, 1970-1980 (Folder 32: 1)
    - Chirac, Jacques, 1969-1980 (Folder 32)
      - 1969-1978 (Folder 32: 2)
      - 1979-1980 (Folder 32: 3)
  - Gendarmerie Nationale, 1942-1945 (Folder 88-89, 57)
    - Clermont-Ferrand, 1943-1945 (Folder 88)
      - 1943 (Folder 88: 5)
      - 1944 (Folder 88: 6)
      - 1945 (Folder 88: 7)
    - Montpellier, 1945 (Folder 88: 8)
    - Paris, 1944-1945 (Folder 88)
      - Nord-Ouest, 1945 (Folder 88: 9)
      - Sud-Ouest, 1944-1945 (Folder 88: 10)
    - Ain, 1942-1943 (Folder 89: 1)
    - Toulouse, 1942-1944 (Folder 89: 2)
    - Limoges, 1943-1944 (Folder 89)
      - 1943 (Folder 89: 3)
      - 1944 (Folder 89: 4)
    - Synthèses nationales, 1945 (Folder 89: 5-6)
    - Alès, 1945 (Folder 57: 5)
    - Alger, 1942-1945 (Folder 57: 6)
    - Grenoble, 1943-1944 (Folder 57: 7)
    - Nice, 1943-1945 (Folder 57: 8)
    - Rabat, 1942-1944 (Folder 57: 9)
    - Tunisie, 1942-1945 (Folder 57)
      - 1942 (Folder 57: 10)
      - 1943 (Folder 57: 11-12)
      - 1944-1945 (Folder 57: 13)
    - Vichy, 1942-1945 (Folder 57: 14)
  - Gendarmerie Nationale, 1942-1947 (Folder 3-4)
    - Générale, 1945 (Folder 3: 2)
    - Besançon, 1943-1945 (Folder 3: 3)
    - Grenoble, 1945 (Folder 3: 4)
    - Lille, 1944-1945 (Folder 3: 5)
    - Limoges, 1944-1945 (Folder 3: 6)
    - Lyon, 1942-1947 (Folder 3: 7-10)
    - Marseille, 1944-1945 (Folder 4: 1)
    - Moulins, 1944-1945 (Folder 4: 2)
    - Nantes, 1945 (Folder 4: 3)
    - Orléans, 1944-1947 (Folder 4: 4)
    - Paris, 1943-1944 (Folder 4: 5)
    - Perpignan, 1945 (Folder 4: 6)
    - Rouen, 1945 (Folder 4: 7)
    - Sud-ouest, 1944-1945 (Folder 4: 8)
    - Toulouse, 1945-1946 (Folder 4: 9)
  - Gendarmerie Nationale, 1942-1947 (Folder 208)
    - Marseille, 1943-1944 (Folder 208: 1)
    - Drôme, 1943-1944 (Folder 208)
      - 1943 (Folder 208: 2)
      - 1944 (Folder 208: 3-5)
  - Georges, Alphonse, 1919-1978 (Folder 110, 220)
    - Discours, 1937 (Folder 110: 2)
    - Lettre, 1914 (Folder 110: 3)
    - Notes, 1919 (Folder 110: 4)
    - Entretiens avec France Georges, 1977-1978 (Folder 110)
      - 1977 (Folder 110: 6)
      - 1978 (Folder 110: 7)
    - Correspondance avec France Georges et Dominique Ader, 1976-1977 (Folder 220: 14)
    - Entretien avec France Georges et Dominique Ader, 1977 (Folder 220: 15)
    - Note du maréchal Foch, 1919 (Folder 220: 16)
    - Mémoires de l'abbé Lambert, 1937 (Folder 220: 17)
  - Gignoux, Claude-Joseph, 1938-1944 (Folder 35-36)
    - Discours, 1938 (Folder 35: 10)
    - l'Opinion, 1942-1944 (Folder 35-36)
      - 1942 (Folder 35: 11-12)
      - 1943 (Folder 36: 1-2)
      - 1944 (Folder 36: 3-4)
  - Giscard d'Estaing, Valéry, 1967-1981 (Folder 104)
    - Activités diverses, 1967-1979 (Folder 104: 3)
    - Dossiers du Canard, 1981 (Folder 104: 4)
    - Commission du Bilan, 1981 (Folder 104: 5)
    - Lettre aux conseillers, 1981 (Folder 104: 6)
  - Goislard de Monsabert, Joseph de, 1932-1965 (Folder 3, 38, 88, 109-110, 365-366)
    - Générale, 1940-1942 (Folder 3: 1)
    - Affaire de Maison-Carrée, 1941 (Folder 38: 4)
    - Index alphabétique, 1965 (Folder 38: 5)
    - Notes de guerre, 1942-1944 (Folder 88: 1)
    - Documents, 1942-1944 (Folder 88)
      - 1942 (Folder 88: 2)
      - 1943 (Folder 88: 3)
      - 1944 (Folder 88: 4)
    - Bulletins, 1932 (Folder 109: 4)
    - Rapports, 1936 (Folder 109: 5)
    - Rapports, 1936 (Folder 110: 1)
    - Bulletins, 1933 (Folder 365-366: 9)
    - Rapports, 1934-1936 (Folder 365)
      - 1934 (Folder 365: 8)
      - 1935 (Folder 365: 9)
      - 1936 (Folder 366: 1-2)
  - Gouvernement Mauroy, 1981-1982 (Folder 30)
    - Hommes du gouvernement, 1981 (Folder 30: 3)
    - Ministres communistes, 1981-1982 (Folder 30: 4-5)
    - Mauroy, Pierre, 1981-1982 (Folder 30: 6-7)
    - Defferre, Gaston, 1981-1982 (Folder 30: 8)
    - Badinter, Robert, 1981-1982 (Folder 30: 9)
    - Delors, Jacques, 1981-1982 (Folder 30: 10)
    - Fabius, Laurent, 1981-1982 (Folder 30: 11)
    - Rocard, Michel, 1982 (Folder 30: 12)
    - Jobert, Michel, 1982 (Folder 30: 13)
  - Goyau, Georges, 1905 (Folder 147: 1-2)
  - Grèves, 1969-1975 (Folder 53-54)
    - Sambron, 1971 (Folder 53: 25)
    - Électricité de France (E.D.F.), 1969 (Folder 53: 26)
    - Houillères du Bassin de Lorraine, 1970-1971 (Folder 53: 27)
    - Batignolles, 1971 (Folder 53: 28)
    - Rateau, 1974 (Folder 53: 29)
    - Joint Français, 1972 (Folder 53: 30)
    - Secteur public, 1974 (Folder 54: 1-2)
    - Moulinex, 1971 (Folder 54: 3)
    - Diverses, 1969-1975 (Folder 54: 4)
  - Grandes réformes, 1977-1982 (Folder 28, 55)
    - L'or, 1981-1982 (Folder 28: 5)
    - Dévaluation du franc, 1981-1982 (Folder 28: 6)
    - Impôt sur la fortune, 1981 (Folder 28: 7-8)
    - Justice, 1981 (Folder 28: 9)
    - Emploi, 1981-1982 (Folder 28: 10-12)
    - École libre, 1981-1982 (Folder 55)
      - 1981 (Folder 55: 1)
      - 1982 (Folder 55: 2)
    - Nationalisations, 1977-1982 (Folder 55)
      - Générale, 1977-1982 (Folder 55)
        - 1977-1981 (Folder 55: 3)
        - 1982 (Folder 55: 4)
      - Assemblée, 1981 (Folder 55: 5)
      - Conseil constitutionnel, 1981-1982 (Folder 55: 6)
      - Opposition, 1981-1982 (Folder 55: 7)
      - Présidents-directeurs Généraux, 1982 (Folder 55: 8)
      - Banques, 1981-1982 (Folder 55: 9)
  - Groupe d'Armées No. 1, 1940 (Folder 15)
    - Messages, 1940 (Folder 15: 7-8)
    - Rapport, 1940 (Folder 15: 9)
  - Hederer, Fernand-entretiens, 1978 (Folder 91: 1-4)
  - Henriot, Philippe, 1941-1976 (Folder 369)
    - Notes, 1974 (Folder 369: 1-2)
    - Assassinat, 1974 (Folder 369: 3)
    - Extraits de témoignages, 1941-1944 (Folder 369: 4)
    - Dac, Pierre, 1973 (Folder 369: 5)
    - Articles, 1973-1976 (Folder 369: 6)
    - Korber, François, 1973 (Folder 369: 7)
    - Sources à exploiter, 1974 (Folder 369: 8)
    - Revues, 1969-1972 (Folder 369: 9)
  - Histoire, 1967-1982 (Folder 52-53)
    - Barbie, Klaus, 1983 (Folder 52: 10)
    - Entre-deux-guerres, 1977 (Folder 53: 1)
    - Veille de la seconde guerre mondiale, 1979 (Folder 53: 2)
    - Seconde guerre mondiale, 1973-1982 (Folder 53: 3)
    - IVe République, 1970-1977 (Folder 53: 4)
    - Indochine, 1979 (Folder 53: 5)
    - Guerre d'Algérie, 1979-1982 (Folder 53: 6)
    - 13 mai 1958, 1973-1978 (Folder 53: 7)
    - Reconversions des soldats perdus, 1970 (Folder 53: 8)
    - Parti Communiste, 1970-1977 (Folder 53: 9)
    - Doriot, Jacques, 1970 (Folder 53: 10)
    - Clémenceau, Georges, 1980 (Folder 53: 11)
    - Lindbergh, Charles, 1977 (Folder 53: 12)
    - Monnet, Jean, 1978-1979 (Folder 53: 13)
    - Touvier, Paul, 1975 (Folder 53: 14)
    - Gouin, Félix, 1970 (Folder 53: 15)
    - Parodi, Alexandre, 1979 (Folder 53: 16)
    - Massé, Pierre, 1978 (Folder 53: 17)
    - Pisar, Samuel, 1979 (Folder 53: 18)
    - Mollet, Guy, 1975 (Folder 53: 19)
    - Pétain, Philippe, 1969-1976 (Folder 53: 20)
    - Juin, Alphonse, 1967 (Folder 53: 21)
    - Darlan, François, 1972-1980 (Folder 53: 22)
    - Heykal, Mohamed, 1975 (Folder 53: 23)
    - Muller, Filip, 1980 (Folder 53: 24)
  - Huntziger, Charles, 1920-1983 (Folder 289-290)
    - Correspondance, 1935-1938 (Folder 289: 27)
    - État des services, 1922 (Folder 289: 28)
    - Notes, 1920-1941 (Folder 289)
      - 1920-1929 (Folder 289: 29)
      - 1938-1939 (Folder 289: 30)
      - 1939 (Folder 289: 31)
      - 1939-1940 (Folder 289: 32)
      - 1940 (Folder 289: 33)
      - 1940-1941 (Folder 289: 34)
      - 1941 (Folder 289: 35)
    - Entretiens, 1983 (Folder 290)
      - Huntziger, Jacques, 1983 (Folder 290: 1-2)
      - Lecomte, Jean, 1983 (Folder 290: 3)
  - L'impuissance et la gloire II, 1918-1973 (Folder 216)
    - Chronologie, 1973 (Folder 216: 3)
    - Traité de Versailles, 1918-1919 (Folder 216: 4)
    - Projet de découpage, 1973 (Folder 216: 5)
  - Indochine, 1918-1939 (Folder 267-269)